A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2 FA390
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
1918-1980
Rockefeller Archive Center
Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman
Harkness, Edward Stephen
Harkness, Charles W.
Commonwealth Fund
Harkness, Anna M. Richardson
FA390
11 Cubic Feet 25 boxes
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research, except where particular restrictions are noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Arrangement note
This series is arranged in 4 subseries:
1 Carleton B. Chapman Files
2 Reginald Fitz Files
3 Quigg Newton Files
4 Barry C. Smith Files
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Other Finding Aids note
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Child welfare; Child psychology; Child mental health; New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Public health; Public welfare; United States; War relief; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Mental health; Medical research; Medicine, Rural; Legal research; Medical education; Law; Legal issues; Education, Rural; Hygiene; Yale University; Social Science Research Council; Harkness, Mary Emma Stillman; Phillips Exeter Academy; Harvard University; Harkness, Edward Stephen; Harkness, Charles W.; Commonwealth Fund; Columbia University; Harkness, Anna M. Richardson
- Carleton B. Chapman Files, 1
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Annual Meetings of the Corporation (54th-61st), November 9, 1972-November 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Annual Meetings of the Corporation (54th-61st), November 9, 1972-November 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Annual Meetings of the Corporation (54th-61st), November 9, 1972-November 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Annual Meetings of the Corporation (54th-61st), November 9, 1972-November 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (215th-222nd), November 9, 1972-February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (215th-222nd), November 9, 1972-February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (215th-222nd), November 9, 1972-February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (215th-222nd), November 9, 1972-February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (215th-222nd), November 9, 1972-February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (215th-222nd), November 9, 1972-February 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (223rd-226th), May 8, 1975-May 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (223rd-226th), May 8, 1975-May 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (223rd-226th), May 8, 1975-May 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (223rd-226th), May 8, 1975-May 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (223rd-226th), May 8, 1975-May 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (223rd-226th), May 8, 1975-May 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (223rd-226th), May 8, 1975-May 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (227th-234th), November 18, 1976-February 8, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (227th-234th), November 18, 1976-February 8, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (227th-234th), November 18, 1976-February 8, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (227th-234th), November 18, 1976-February 8, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (227th-234th), November 18, 1976-February 8, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (227th-234th), November 18, 1976-February 8, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (235th-238th), May 10, 1979-May 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (235th-238th), May 10, 1979-May 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (235th-238th), May 10, 1979-May 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (235th-238th), May 10, 1979-May 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (235th-238th), May 10, 1979-May 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Board of Directors Meetings (235th-238th), May 10, 1979-May 8, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Conference of Foundations on Needs in Health, July 19, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Correspondence - Corporation and Board of Directors, February 9, 1973-July 22, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Executive Committee Meeting, June 25, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Grant Reviews and Summaries - General, 1949-1979 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Grant Reviews and Summaries - Medical Schools, 1949-1977 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Grant Reviews and Summaries - Medical Schools and Medical Education, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Grant Reviews and Summaries - New York City, 1958-1979 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Board of Directors and Corporation Records - Miscellaneous Board Material, January 9, 1968-December 10, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Christmas Letters to Fellows, 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Announcement), November 20, 1975-March 22, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests), January 1976-February 1976 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests), January 1976-February 1976 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests), March 1976-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests), March 1976-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests), March 1976-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests), March 1976-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests), March 1976-December 1976 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Aldrich, Hulbert (Cutback-Protests - Report), May 5, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Correspondence - Fellows to Carleton B. Chapman, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Dinners and Parties, February 20, 1976-September 30, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fellowship Report - Meeting of October 17, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fellowship Report - Meeting of November 13, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fellowship Review, 1925-1974 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fellowships - Australia, May 1, 1978-April 8, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fellowships - New Zealand, May 1, 1978-July 2, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fellowships - United Kingdom, January 7, 1980-November 13, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fellowships - United Kingdom (Applications), 1976 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Fulbright Correspondence, April 5, 1975-June 28, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - General Correspondence, January 5, 1973-December 8, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - General Correspondence, January 8, 1974-June 8, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - London Office Correspondence, August 22, 1977-May 8, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - London Office Correspondence, August 22, 1977-May 8, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - London Office Correspondence, August 22, 1977-May 8, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - London Office Correspondence, August 22, 1977-May 8, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Meeting - Harkness Committee Representatives, Paris, October 23, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Meeting - Subcommittee on Fellowships, October 31, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Meeting - On Fellowships, September 10, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Meeting - On Fellowships, September 10, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Meeting - On Fellowships, September 10, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Meeting - Chairmen and Selection Committee, November 7-8, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 76)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Memorandum, September 1, 1978-June 9, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Memorandum, September 1, 1978-June 9, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Memorandum, September 1, 1978-June 9, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 79)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - New York Office Correspondence, October 15, 1973-December 21,1978 (Box 10, Folder 80)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - New York Office Correspondence, October 15, 1973-December 21,1978 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - New York Office Correspondence, October 15, 1973-December 21,1978 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - New York Office Correspondence, October 15, 1973-December 21,1978 (Box 10, Folder 83)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - New York Office Correspondence, January 4, 1979-November 4, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Reports, April 1957-September 1978 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Reports, April 1957-September 1978 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Reports, April 1957-September 1978 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Reports, April 1957-September 1978 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Reports, April 1957-September 1978 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Reports, April 1957-September 1978 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Reports, April 1957-September 1978 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Search for Director of Harkness Fellowship Program, July 12, 1978-September 10, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - Australia and New Zealand, April 15-30, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - Australia and New Zealand, April 15-30, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 94)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - Australia and New Zealand, April 15-30, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - Australia and New Zealand, April 15-30, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - Australia and New Zealand, April 15-30, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 97)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, September 17-23, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 98)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, January 22-24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, January 22-24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, June 15-22, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, June 15-22, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, January 18-25, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, January 16-23, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, January 16-23, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, October 24-28, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London (Cancelled), January 30, 1978-February 3,1978 (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Visit - London, September 11-13, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Harkness Fellowship Program - Wellcome Trust, July 2, 1973-October 19, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Al-Bu), February-July 1974 (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Al-Bu), February-July 1974 (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Ch-Pa), February-July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Ch-Pa), February-July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Ch-Pa), February-July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Ch-Pa), February-July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Ch-Pa), February-July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Ch-Pa), February-July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Ch-Pa), February-July 1974 (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Pe-Zu), February-July 1974 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Pe-Zu), February-July 1974 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Pe-Zu), February-July 1974 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Pe-Zu), February-July 1974 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Correspondence with Fellows (Pe-Zu), February-July 1974 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Letters of Inquiry, November 14, 1973-March 26, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 124)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - List and Summary, February 27, 1974-May 21, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Report on Inquiry, July 1, 1973-May 3, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Summary of Fellowship Awards - Ten Year Period (July 1, 1956-June 30, 1966), December 1967 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Ten Year Period (July 1, 1956-June 30, 1966), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Ten Year Period (July 1, 1956-June 30, 1966), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Survey of Domestic Fellows - Ten Year Period (July 1, 1956-June 30, 1966), 1974 (Box 16, Folder 130)
- Reginald Fitz Files, 2
  - American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) - October 24-27, 1976 Meeting - Correspondence and Paper, March 19, 1976-February 13, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 131)
  - Draft/Data for American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) Paper - General, June 20, 1973-August 27, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 132)
  - Draft/Data for American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) Paper - Tufts, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 133)
  - Draft/Data for American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) Paper - Tufts, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 134)
  - Draft/Data for American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) Paper - Tulane, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Draft/Data for American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) Paper - Tulane, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  - Draft/Data for American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) Paper - Vanderbilt, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  - Draft/Data for American Clinical and Climatological Association (ACCA) Paper - Vanderbilt, 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 138)
  - Report on the Commonwealth Scholarship Program of 1932-1944 (John Wilber), October 1975 (Box 17, Folder 139)
- Quigg Newton Files, 3
  - Harkness Fellowships - Aldrich, Malcolm P. (Notes on London Meeting), April 29, 1968-May 2, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 140)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Committee of Award - Meeting in London (Correspondence), January 28, 1974-February 2, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 141)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Committee of Award - Meeting in London (Reports), January 28, 1974-February 2, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 142)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Committee of Award - Nomination Committees, March 8, 1967-July 3, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 143)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Confidential Correspondence, February 19, 1965-December 28, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted material.
  - Harkness Fellowships - Cullen, John, November 25, 1968-August 5, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 145)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Cutback - Ashby, Sir Eric, September 21, 1967-March 19, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 146)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Cutback - Australia, October 17, 1967-April 30, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 147)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Cutback - Belgium, France and Germany, December 27, 1967-April 15, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Cutback - Italy and Commonwealth Fund London Office, October 5, 1967-April 30, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 149)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Cutback - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Netherlands, November 10, 1967-April 23, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 150)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Cutback - New Zealand and United Kingdom, October 6, 1967-May 20, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 151)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Albemarle, Lord and Lady, November 23, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 152)
  - Harkness Fellowships - Dinner - Ashby, Sir Eric and Lady, June 15, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 153)